<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Hassan Films</title>
    <link>https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Hassan Films</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:01:30 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pan&#39;s Labyrinth - Review</title>
      <link>https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/pan-s-labyrinth-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 23:01:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/pan-s-labyrinth-review/</guid>
      <description>Guillermo del Toro took an interesting turn into the darkness with Pan’s Labyrinth. Just from the title and a few posters I’ve seen, I was not ready for this to be a fairytale. Although, I was expecting a mystical world with the most unreal and non-human like creatures but events of the Spanish Civil War going on in the background gave this film a terrifying touch which was actually what got me interested in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life of Pi Review</title>
      <link>https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/life-of-pi-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:53:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/life-of-pi-review/</guid>
      <description>The argument between believing versus not believing Pi’s story has been the outcome for me after watching Life of Pi. There was a lot of realistic events happening in this film before Pi went through the Journey which may have made the storyline a little tedious. There were some unnecessary inclusions in the plot such as the added romance between Pi and Anandi which didn’t make any sense towards the story’s flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ratatouille - Review</title>
      <link>https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/ratatouille-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 10:17:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hassanfilms-8d2e4.web.app/blog/ratatouille-review/</guid>
      <description>Rats and restaurants don’t go well together for our society to prosper. The idea of a rat entering a space where food is present is the most taboo event that can occur in a kitchen. Pixar broke exactly that rule by creating this piece of art. There are several reasons that make Ratatouille one of my favorite Pixar movies. Looking at Remy make those exquisite dishes makes me want to get up and do the same.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
